And every single generation or every single usage that we have out of this tool, our credits will start being loose, you know, or something like that.
And as you see, document actions take one credit, generate outline, takes one credit, generate draft.
So the exact same thing that we're doing right here takes two credits and video summary takes four credits.
So let me come back here to see if there are any pricing or any pro plan that we can upgrade to.
Are there any, so let me search for it.
So as I say, jotbots pro, right?
And jotbot pricing, let's say.
So I can't see anything over here.
There are several reserves and pricing options.
So whatever, let's come here to see if there are any.
Okay, it doesn't matter for now, but there has to be some way to get out of these credits, right?
Oh, upgrade to unlimited, right?
So this button has been in front of us for all this time and I've been looking for it with Google search.
It's very weird.
But whatever, as you see, we have a free option and we have an unlimited option that is build $14 per month, right?
Probably US dollars.